Five cards, four, three, two, one.
Hackey-yoi! Kami Shiba!
No, no, no.
God.
Yes, sir.
Yes, one more time.
Hake-yoi! Kami Sumo!
Applause
Come on, let's play sumo with me!
Do you know what sumo is?
I do.
Let me just explain.
People fight each other like this.
Correct.
Thank you.
Correct. Thank you. You're right.
Ding-dong!
It's a traditional event where men fight each other.
Today you brought a doll with your favorite picture on it, right?
Yes, I did.
I brought it.
For the camera.
But now it's done... and we're going to have them fight in a ring made of this paper.
Now, when I say I didn't hear you say that clearly, just tap here.
The first one to move the doll out of the ring loses.
It's about who falls over or doesn't fall over.
Yes, sir.
And we're gonna give away some cool stuff to the winner.
Good luck.
Okay, then, who'll play with me first, Ayumu?
Yes, sir.
Please come forward.
Okay.
Okay, I'll do this.
What did Ayumu make for me?
It's a penguin.
A penguin.
A penguin. Penguin.
I'm a bear.
Maybe bears are stronger than bears.
No, I don't know yet.
What's with all the red around you? Is it motivation?
Oh, that's good. Then let's fight.
Okay, let's fight.
Unleash the power!
Yay!
I'm going to leave it at this foundation.
Oh, you went easy on me?
I won.
You're stronger than that, really.
Well, Penguin, you lose!
Please put me down.
I was held back... by a child.
Okay, next...
Yuriya and Takemei will fight.
How do you feel about a showdown between brothers?
How do you feel about a showdown at Tokyo University?
What do you think?
What is this?
Ladybugs.
Where's that fried chicken? What happened to it?
It's not fried, it's a dog.
Oh, dog?
Ladybug?
What? Fried? What's this? Fried? A dog.
Dog.
It's a dog.
Are you sure it's a traditional bug? It's really a dog.
It's a little weak, don't you think? Are you okay?
All right, let's go.
That's all that's left! Let's see who wins.
Whoa!
If you let them out of the ring, you win.
If you let them out of the ring, you lose. If you let them out of the ring, you lose.
Yes, the electric bug is still weak.
You're early, you're leaving early.
I won, Yuriya-chan. How's it going?
You don't seem to be in a good mood.
Next, it's me and Shiori-chan. Who is it? Who is it?
Maybe it's the opposite.
We're exactly the same.
I made a mistake.
I'm not taking a human being with me.
I'll go then.
All right, I got it.
Oh, man.
He's so strong!
Yo-chan wins!
She's so strong!
Amazing! Humans are the strongest!
Next, Kurumi and Yuriya.
Team competition?
One of you, this way.
Okay, Kurumi, this way.
What's that?
Penguin.
And this one?
Human.
Penguin versus human.
What do you think? Do you think we can win?
Do you think we can win?
I'm motivated.
Shall we go?
Okay. All right.
We're left!
Which way?
Oh, I lost!
Yuriya wins!
I lost!
Yuriya versus Hiyori. Let's see, Yuriya vs Hiyori
The Final
We've fought all the way to this point, and now it's time for the final!
Yuriya and Hiyori are the same.
Huh? Huh? Huh? Huh?
What? What is it? What's happening?
Huh? Disappeared? Disappeared? Oh, he's here, isn't he? Oh, my God. Huh? Huh? What? What? What happened? Huh? Is he gone?
Is he here? What? No, no, no, no, no.
I'm not here, I'm not here, I'm not here.
It's so weird.
There's a strange atmosphere here.
Mr. Hiyori and Ms. Yuriya.
Please come!
They won't come unless I call them "sir".
What's going on?
Oh, my God... he's got a bad temper.
What shall I do?
I want to finish it.
It's right this way.
Let's cheer for them.
At the end of the finals, whoever wins this gets something.
Okay, but let's get started.
Let's have each of you say how you feel.
Ms. Hiyori.
Yes, sir.
Yes.
I want to win
I want to win.
Can we win?
Yes. - Yes.
Yes, sir.
I was just saying that we both know we can win.
Well...
Hachoo.
Remain.
Go, go, go, go, go, go!
Go, Arjun, you're winning! Go Arwa!
Hiyori's winning!
Just great work by the Penguins to get this far!
What a win!
Well, Hiyori-sama...
TV Asahi.
And for me, from TV Asahi.
Thank you very much.
What did you think of it today?
It's close.
Thank you for taking care of me, and don't look so glad you didn't win.
I didn't get in.
You're the cutest thing I've ever seen.